Welcome back.
In this section we are talking about system services in Android.
Almost all the apps in an Android device communicates with system services.
Here is the architecture and diagram of Android and we could clearly see that System Services is a bridge
between the apps or app framework and the hardware abstraction layer.
For example, when we take a photo using camera, we communicate through the system services to the
camera hardware drivers.
There are mainly two categories of system servers, the media server and the system.
So media server handlers, media player, camera, etc. system server handlers, search window manager,
etc...